A Finding Aid to the William P. Daley Papers, 1905-2016 (bulk 1951-2001), in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Exhibition Files, 1949-1999, undated; Series 3; Archival Resource Key; 2.7 Linear feet Boxes 3-5
  - Exhibition Files, 1949-1998, undated; 3.1; Archival Resource Key
    - Pottery Questions II (1985), 1984-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Pennsylvania Ceramists: The Container (1984), 1984-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - William Daley Vessels at Braunstein Gallery (1985), 1984-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Architectural Clay/Clay in Architecture (1985), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - "Big Containment" (1986), 1985-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Contemporary Arts: An Expanding View (1986), 1985-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - "Contemporary Crafts: A Concept in Flux" (1986), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - 27th Ceramic National Exhibition (1987), 1986-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - "Contemporary American Ceramics" (1987), 1986-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Investigations of the Mind (1987), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - "Ceramic Artists: Works on Paper" (1987), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Craft Today: Poetry of the Physical (1987-1988), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Craft Today: USA (1988-1992), 1986-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - William Daley at Garth Clark Gallery (1988), 1987-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - New Art Forms (1988), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - William Daley at Helen Drutt Gallery (1988), 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - "Oval Chamber" at the Renwick Gallery (1988), 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - American Clay Artists 1989, 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Clay/Fiber/Metal Invitational 1989, 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Contemporary Artifacts 1989, Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - "Faculty Drawing Exhibition at the University of the Arts" (1989), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - "Mirror Images" (1989), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - International Ceramics Competition '89, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - William Daley: 1990-1980, Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 37-39)
    - Montgomery County Artists Invitational Art Show (1990), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - William Daley at Helen Drutt Gallery (1990), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - "Visiting Artists Program: 20th Year Anniversary Show" (1991), 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Scale/Detail (1991), 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - National Ceramic Invitational at West Chester University (1992), 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - "Impressions Through Plaster" (1992), 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Philadelphia College of Art Exhibition, 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - A Decade of Craft: Recent Acquisitions at the American Craft Museum (1992), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Contemporary Crafts by Pennsylvanian Artists (1992), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Inside/Outside: Ceramics and Drawings by William Daley (1993), 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Contemporary American Ceramics at Stetson University (1993), 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - The Year of American Craft (1993), 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - UnConventional Art (1993), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Distinguished Alumni Exhibition at Columbia University (1993), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Wustum Museum of Fine Arts, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - William Daley: Ceramic Works and Drawings (1993), 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 55-56)
    - Drawing '94: Explorations, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - William Daley: Ceramic Works and Drawings at the Renwick Gallery (1994), Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 58-60)
    - William Daley: Ceramic Works and Drawings at the Arkansas Art Center (1994), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Working in Other Dimensions: Objects and Drawings II (1994), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Clay Studio 20th Anniversary Celebration Exhibition (1994), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - 4th International Ceramics Symposium, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Vessels: Three Views (1995), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - William Daley: Ceramic Works and Drawings (1995), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Influenced by Nature (1995-1996), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Wood Turning Center Exhibition (1997), 1995-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Pennsylvania Treasures I (1998), 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Sculpture Objects and Functional Art at SOFA New York, 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Mid-Atlantic Contemporary Tile (1998), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Regis Master Series (1998), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Paper Pots II (1998), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous Materials, 1962-1963, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Auction Files, 1979-1993, undated; 3.2; Archival Resource Key
    Auction Files contain material relating to art auctions for which Daley donated a work of art. Found are correspondence, price lists, printed materials, including catalogs and announcements, and receipts. Files are arranged chronologically by year of auction.
    - Channel 12 Art & Antiques Auction, 1979-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Haystack Auction 1980, Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - American Craft Museum Selection '85, 1985, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Haystack Silent Auction, 1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - American Craft Museum Bewitched by Craft, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Clay Studio Ceramic Art Sweepstakes, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Christie's, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Wallingford Potters Guild, 1990-1992, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - "Touchstone Auction", 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Exhibition Juror Files, 1968-1999; 3.3; Archival Resource Key
    The Exhibition Juror Files contain material concerning exhibitions for which Daley was a juror or critic. Materials in these files are very similar to the Exhibitions files and typically include correspondence, expense lists and receipts, award lists, and printed materials, including announcements, brochures, and press clippings. Files are arranged chronologically by year of exhibition.
    - "York Sate Craft Fair", 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Delaware Art Museum Annual Contemporary Crafts Exhibition (1973), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Show of Crafts and Graphics (1978), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Philadelphia Craft Show (1979), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Arts Alive '81, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Michigan Ceramics/Rouge 1982, 1981-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Boston University "Certificate of Mastery Exhibition", 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - New Directions in Tile (1983), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Pennsylvania Guild of Craftsmen (1984), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Designed and Made for Use (1985), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Market House '86, 1985-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Swain School of Design Graduate Exhibition (1986), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Abington Art Center Ceramic Exhibition (1988), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Main Line Center of the Arts 25th Annual Craft Exhibition (1988), 1988-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - "New Jersey Art Educators As Artists" (1990), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - National Museum of Ceramic Art First Regional Juried Exhibition (1991), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Louis Comfort Tiffany Foundation (1991), 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - "Fleischer Art Memorial Challenge Competition" (1992-1993), 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Wallingford Potters Guild (1992), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Clay Here and There (1993), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - "Members/Faculty Exhibition" at Perkins Center for the Arts (1994), 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Strictly Functional Pottery National Exhibit (1994), 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Smithsonian Craft Show (1995), 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Abington Friends School Celebrate Crafts, 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - University of the Arts MFA Winter Critique, 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Pew Fellowship in the Arts, 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Clay Studio Exhibition (1997), 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Ceramics '97, 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - 1997 Central Pennsylvania Festival of the Arts, 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Wayne Art Center: Craft Forms '98, 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Project Files, 1956-2000, undated; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; 1 Linear foot Boxes 5-6
  Project Files typically contain correspondence, expense lists, receipts, sketches, printed material, and photographs related to sculpture projects that William Daley completed or proposed during his career. This includes public and private commissions, notably a sculpture for IBM at the Seattle World's Fair, a sculpture for South African Airways, the Fairfield Maxwell Wall, and work completed at the Westminster Presbyterian Church. Files are arranged chronologically by year.
  - Works in Feasterville, Pennsylvania, 1956-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - "Timeless Metronome", 1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - "Progeny", circa 1959, 1975, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Casablanca International Trade Fair, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - "Columbine", 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - John Pickett Fountain, circa 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Robert John Sculpture, circa 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - IBM at Seattle World's Fair Sculpture, 1961-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 61-63)
  - Colgate Research Center Mural, 1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Ceramic and Teak Wood Screens, 1962-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - State University of New York, Fredonia Senior Class Present, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - "Centurian Marker", 1964, 1996-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 67-68)
  - Works in Fredonia, New York, 1964-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Penn State Planters, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Lillian Garabedian Memorial, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - ARCO Chemical Company Sculpture, 1966-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - TAP Portuguese Airways Sculpture, 1966-1968, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - "Burning Bush", circa 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Hallenwall Realty Company Sculpture, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - John Pickett Fireplace, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Haddington Recreation Center Fountain, 1970-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - South African Airways Sculpture, 1970-1971, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 7-9)
  - Germantown Friends School Sculpture, 1970-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 10-11)
  - Fairfield Maxwell Wall, 1971-1979, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 12-14)
  - North American Watch Co. Sculpture, circa 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Campbell Soup Tureen, 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Our Lady of the Rosary Baptismal Font, 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Squire Enterprises, Inc. Flower Pots, 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Ritz Motion Picture Theatre Sculpture, 1977-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 19-21)
  - Certainteed Corp. Fountain, 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - NEA "Art in Public Places" Inquiry, 1979, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Earl Millard Pot, 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Wills Eye Hospital Wall, 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal Church Baptismal Font, 1988-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Studio Potter Network Drawing, 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Arrow International, Inc. Sculpture, 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Westminster Presbyterian Church, 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 29-30)
  - Sam Schacht Drawings, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Arrow International, Inc. Wall Segment, 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Wayne Bates Dormer, 1996-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Workshops, Seminars, and Lectures, 1958-1998, undated; Series 5; Archival Resource Key; 2.3 Linear feet Boxes 6-8
  This series includes extensive materials on workshops William Daley taught, seminars he participated in, and lectures that he gave on topics of art, ceramics, and education. Files typically contain most or all of the following: correspondence, expense lists and receipts, schedules of events, lecture or teaching notes, printed material, including brochures and press clippings, and photographs of the event. Files are labeled according to location or title of the event and are arranged chronologically by year.
  - NBC's "Adventuring in the Hand Arts", 1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - General Motors Summer Program, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - South Senior High School, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - World of Arts Raku Workshop, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Waldorf College, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Collab '71, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - California College of Arts and Crafts, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - University of Cincinnati, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Montgomery County Community College, 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Board of Education and Philadelphia Art Alliance "Artist to Artist Program", 1976-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Ohio State University, 1976-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Alfred University, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - "Jam Craft Media Day & Exhibition", 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Arts Council Program, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - William Allen High School, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Philadelphia College of Art's Law and Art Seminar, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Cleveland Institute of Art, 1977-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Cranbrook Academy of Art, 1977-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Rhode Island School of Design, 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Institute of Contemporary Art, University of Pennsylvania, 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - University of Rhode Island, 1978-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - NCECA/SuperMud Conference, 1978-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Exhibit A: Peter Voulkos Exhibit, 1979, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - University of Pennsylvania "Continuum", 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Drexel University, 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Purdue University, 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Banff Center Summer Session, 1979-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 60-61)
  - Stockton State College, 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - "Contemporary American Potter" Symposium, 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - NCECA 1980, Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Avila College, 1980-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - "Ceramics Seminar '81", 1980-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - "International Ceramics Symposium 1981", 1980-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Art Sales and Rental Gallery Talk, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Philadelphia Museum of Art "Celebration of Crafts", 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Manayunk Art Center, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Fredonia State University College, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - NCECA 1981, Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Consortium: 80/81, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - University of Colorado at Boulder, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Emily Carr College of Art, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - University of Texas at Austin, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Swarthmore College, 1982, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - NCECA 1983, 1982-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Luther College Artists Visit, 1982-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Blossom Festival School Art Program, 1982-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - NCECA Boston '84, 1983-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Napa Valley College, 1983-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Anderson Ranch Arts Center, 1983-1984, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - School of Art, Kutztown State College, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Long Beach Island Foundation, 1984-1985, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - American Potters Today, 1984-1986; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Chautauqua Institution, 1984-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Temple University, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Kansas City Art Institute, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Friends Seminary, 1985, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Clay Studio, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - NCECA '85, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Nova Scotia College of Art and Design, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Architecture of the Vessel Symposium, 1985-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - "University of Arkansas NEA Visiting Artists Forum Series", 1985-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Connecticut Clay Artists, 1985-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Alfred College, 1985, 1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Chicago International New Art Form Exposition, 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - NCECA 1986, Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Art/Culture/Future: American Craft '86 Conference, 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Greenwich House Pottery Workshop, 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Lill Street Gallery Fall Education Series, 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Plattsburg State University College, 1986-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - College Art Association Meetings, 1986-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - NCECA '97, 1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - University of South Carolina, 1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Harbourfront "International Creators" Lecture Series, 1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Market House Craft Center, 1987-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Symposium: The Case for Clay in Secondary Education, 1987-1988, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Clay in the East IV Symposium, 1987-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Hartwick College, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Mercersburg Academy Workshop, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Camden County College, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Baylor University, 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - University of Manitoba, 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Haystack Mountain School of Crafts, 1988-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 48-49)
  - NCECA '89, 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Princeton University, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - "Montclair State College Art Forum", 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - University of Michigan School of Art, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Main Line Center of the Arts, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Banff Centre School of Fine Arts, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - "Clayfolk"/Southern Oregon State College, 1989-1990, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Cheltenham Art Centre, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Southern Illinois University Visiting Artist, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - University of Miami, 1989-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Chautauqua Institution, 1989-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Functional Ceramics Workshop, 1989-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Cranbrook Academy of Art, 1990, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - James Renwick Alliance, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - NCECA '90, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Arvada Center for the Arts and Humanities, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Radcliff Ceramics Studio, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Whitemarsh Art Center, 1990, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Converse College, 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Peters Valley Craftsmen, 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Arkansas Art Center, 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Penland School of Crafts, 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Northern Illinois University, 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Touchstone Center for Crafts, 1990-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Art and Industry Forum, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Nova Scotia College of Art and Design, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Johns Hopkins University School of Continuing Studies, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - NCECA 1991, Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Conversations '91, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 78-79)
  - Haystack Mountain School of Crafts, 1991, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 1)